edoqs.net 2014-02-23

# Privacy policy - edoqs

## PRIVACY AND SECURITY

The statement below outlines the _edoqs_ website Privacy Policy. _edoqs_ may update its Privacy Policy to reflect changes in the products and services that _edoqs_ offers, however, the underlying goal of protecting user privacy remains the same. By using _edoqs_ service, each user consents to the collection, use or disclosure of their Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the _edoqs_ service following the "last-revised" date on this Privacy Policy will represent your consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy as modified. You are advised to review this page regularly for any changes. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or feel that _edoqs_ has not complied with the Policy, they should first contact us via contact form. 

## STORAGE AND USE OF USER INFORMATION 

_edoqs_ stores information as described below that could be used to idenfify users (Personal Information") on the _edoqs_ servers for the sole purpose of providing the _edoqs_ service to users. _edoqs_ also stores certain non-personally identifiable information using log files. 

The following paragraph describes the Personal Information collected on _edoqs_ servers: email address, name and mailing address, telephone number, payment and usage records. 

## ELIGIBILITY 

Use of _edoqs_ web site and all related services by children under the age of 13 is strictly prohibited. _edoqs_ reserves the right to delete, move, edit, refuse to post or take other appropriate action with respect to any messages, information or files which _edoqs_ , in its sole discretion, deems objectionable or otherwise in violation of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.

## COOKIES 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users' computer or cellular phone tied to information about the user. _edoqs_ uses session ID cookies. However, the user must opt-in to the usage of cookies by indicating that their login credentials be remembered when they login in subsequent sessions. _edoqs_ may also use cookies that are not linked to any Personal Information to store certain preferences about the user's use of the services. For example, cookies may be used to allow a user to set a preference to skip a verification screen when capturing information. 

## AGGREGATE INFORMATION 

_edoqs_ may use users' Personal Information to generate aggregated information that does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted. Aggregated Information shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and may be used by _edoqs_ to provide insight on the usage of the _edoqs_ services. 

_edoqs_ allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. 

## WEB AND MOBILE INTERNET SITE ACTIVITY 

Like most standard Web and mobile internet sites, _edoqs_ stores and uses web server log files. These files include anonymous information about web browsers, such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, dateikrne stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Such log files are not linked to Personal Information through the _edoqs_ service. 

## SHARING 

_edoqs_ will not share any information provided by users, except as follows: 

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) _edoqs_ may use users' Personal Information to generate aggregated information relating to activity on _edoqs_ -enabled products and services. This aggregate information does not allow the user to be personally identified or contacted and shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis. This information is shared with relevant _edoqs_ customers and partners. 

When _edoqs_ Discloses User Information _edoqs_ may share users' Personal Information with its affiliates, subsidiaries and service providers for the sole purpose of providing the _edoqs_ service to the user, provided that the information is required for and used only for such purpose and provided the information is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. _edoqs_ will otherwise only release Personal Information to third parties in the following limited circumstances: (i) if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires _edoqs_ to do so; (ii) if _edoqs_ 's rights or property or the rights or property of _edoqs_ 's affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers or the users of _edoqs_ 's web site or services are in jeopardy; or (iii) if the personal safety of users of _edoqs_ 's web site or services or other members of the public is in jeopardy. 

## LINKS 

This Web or mobile interne( site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that _edoqs_ is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. _edoqs_ encourages its users to be aware when they leave the _edoqs_ site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personal Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the _edoqs_ web and interaet mobile site. 

## SECURITY 

_edoqs_ employs security measures in order to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, theft and alteration of Personal Information under _edoqs_ 's control. However, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Consequently, _edoqs_ , its affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers and their respective officers, directors, employees and agents do not represent, warrant or guarantee that Personal Information will be protected against misuse, loss or alterations and do not accept any liability for Personal Information submitted to or collected by them nor for your or third parties' use or misuse of Personal Information. 

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

Should _edoqs_ decide to change its privacy policy, changes to this privacy statement will be posted on the _edoqs_ web site. 

## CONTACT INFORMATION

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding _edoqs_ 's privacy policy, please use _edoqs_ contact form.
